University of Connecticut, Vice President and Chief Operating Officer Records 2006.0171
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
University of Connecticut, Vice President and Chief Operating Officer Records
undated, 1875-1986.
2006.0171
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
32.55 Linear feet
Office records for the office responsible for the administration of operations and fiscal activities for the University of Connecticut.
University of Connecticut, Office of the Vice President and Chief Operating Officer.
History
the COO is responsible for overseeing construction, renovation, operation, logistics and security of the University's physical plant; human resources and payroll; purchasing; accounts payable; information technology; business services; and public and environmental safety, as well as formulation of strategy and policies to ensure effective administration, sound business practices, safety and regulatory compliance within these areas, in conformity with policies established by the board of trustees. http://www.uconn.edu/administration/vp_coo.php
Finance and Administration separated into two departments in 1988 and reunited in 1991. The responsibilities were again separated in 2000 with the appointment of Lorraine Aronson.
Chief Clerk and Purchasing Agent, Treasurer, Comptroller
Raymond I. Longley, 1916-1943
Comptroller
Leonard C. Riccio, 1943-1958/9
Vice President for Finance and Administration
John M. Evans, 1960-1973
Richard J. DeHaan, 1973-1975
Harry J. Hartley 1975-1978
C. Edward Hanna (acting), 1978-1979
Arthur L. Gillis, 1979-1984
Harry J. Hartley, 1984-1988
Wilbur R. Jones, 1991-1998
Vice President for Finance
Thomas R. Popplewell, (interim), 1988-1989
Wilbur R. Jones, 1989-1991
Vice President for Administration
Sallie A. Giffen, 1988-1991
Vice President for Operations
Dale Dreyfus, 1998-2005
Vice President and Chief Financial Officer
Lorraine Aronson, 2000-2008
Richard Gray, 2008-
Vice President and Chief Operating Officer
Linda Flaherty-Goldsmith, -2006
Barry Feldman, 2006-2012
Scope and Content
The records of this office pertain to the administrative operations involved in the everyday activities of the University--budget, finance, payroll, human resources, facilities, etc. The collection contains correspondence, reports, studies, minutes, financial and legal records, publications, photographs and maps. Of special interest are the legal records in Series IV and Series VIII, which provide insight into the physical growth and expansion of the University in the late 19th and early 20th centuries. A small glimpse into the lives of Depression-era students, while attending and afterwards, can be extrapolated from the correspondence with the Student Loan Committee in Series V. The records of the VP &CFO (2000-) are described in the finding aid for that office.
Arrangement
The records of several administrative tenures have been combined to form the following series:
Series I: Administrative Records ( undated, 1908-1986 ) includes correspondence, reports, studies, minutes and related materials from several tenures.
Series II: Construction Projects ( undated, 1896-1970 ) includes correspondence, legal and financial records pertaining to construction at the University, primarily on the Storrs campus.
Series III: Vendor Materials ( 1916-1977 ) contains contracts, brochures and correspondence with companies doing business with the institution.
Series IV: Property Transfers and Bequests ( undated, 1875-1972 ) includes copies of deeds and related legal documents pertaining to the transfer of property to or from the University.
Series V: Student Loan Committee Correspondence ( 1920-1936 ) includes correspondence between the committee and alumni of the institution in regard to the repayment of loans.
Series VI: Photographs ( undated ) contains photographs removed from Series I-V.
Series VII: Oversize Materials ( undated, 1915-1975 ) contains oversize maps, blueprints and plats extracted from Series I-V, as well as loose in the collection.
Series VIII: Financial Records ( undated, 1899-1930 ) contains ledgers and payroll records from the early years of the institution. These records provide insight into the activities and programs at the University during years in which the administrative records are incomplete. Materials transferred from the VP&CFO Office are described in the finding aid for that office.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
By-Laws of the Univeristy of Connecticut Faculty-Alumni Center. Dodd
By-Laws of the University of Connecticut Foundation. Dodd
Enrollment at State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, Fall 1977. Dodd
Guide to thoughtful giving and estate planning. Dodd
Higher Cost of a Higher Education. Undergraduate Trends in New England, 1970-1975. Dodd
Plan for the development of the School of Law of the University of Connecticut. Dodd
Report on the Development Program of the University of Connecticut and recommendations for a master plan leading to a major centennial campaign. Dodd
Student Charges at State and Land-Grant Universities. Dodd Periodicals
Undergraduate course programs of 1,612, 1965 University of Connecticut graduates. Dodd
Undergraduate quality point ratios of 1,612 1965 University of Connecticut graduates. Dodd
University of Connecticut 1970. Dodd
University of Connecticut Reconnaissance Survey. Dodd
Acquisition Information
The materials in the collection have been transferred in installments over the years from the office(s) reporting to this administrative unit.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to the University, its history, administration, faculty, staff and students. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
University of Connecticut. Administration.; University of Connecticut. Office of the Vice President and Chief Operating Officer.; Administrative Records.; Archives.; Blueprints.; College administrators.; Contracts.; Correspondence.; Financial Records.; Maps.; Minutes.; Notes.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Press releases.; Publications.; Storrs (Conn.); Universities and colleges--United States--Administration.; Universities and colleges--United States--Finance.; University of Connecticut.
- Series I: Administrative Records, undated, 1908-1986
  - AAUP, 1976-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Accidents, 1967-1972 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Act chaning name of institution, 1933, 1939 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Action items--Complaints, 1979-1980 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Administration Building, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Admissions, 1973-1977 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action, 1974-1977 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, 1977-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action Plan Committee, 1974-1976 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action Program, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Afro-American Students, Organization of, 1975-1977 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Agenda--Board meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Agriculture, 1975-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Agriculture, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - Agriculture, State Department of, 1967-1971 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - Air Conditioning, 1974-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - Alcoholism Program, 1974-1976 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - Aleutian Expedition, 1971 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - Algonquin Gas, 1965-1969 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
  - Allied Health Professions, 1970-1975 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
  - Allotments, 1967-1978 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Association (Box 1:, Folder 23)
  - American Society of COmposers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), 1978 (Box 1:, Folder 24)
  - Analysis of Salry and Wage needs, 1976-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
  - Andrus Fund, 1966 (Box 1:, Folder 26)
  - Animal Care Center, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 27)
  - Annuities, 1969-1976 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
  - Appraisals, 1970 (Box 1:, Folder 29)
  - Apprenticeship Program, 1976-1980 (Box 1:, Folder 30)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 1:, Folder 31)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1978 (Box 1:, Folder 32)
  - Appropriations Committee, 1979 (Box 1:, Folder 33)
  - Asbestos Problem--Brundage Pool, 1977-1978 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
  - Asset Management, 1978-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 35)
  - Associated Student Commissaries, 1970-1972 (Box 1:, Folder 36)
  - Associated Student Commissaries, 1974-1978 (Box 1:, Folder 37)
  - Associated Student Commissaries, 1975-1979 (Box 1:, Folder 38)
  - Associated Student Government, 1970-1971 (Box 1:, Folder 39)
  - Athletics, Division of Intercollegiate, 1974-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 40)
  - Athletics, Division of Intercollegiate, 1979 (Box 2:, Folder 41)
  - Attorney General's Office, 1955-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 42)
  - Auditorium (ANJ), 1964-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 43)
  - Auditor, Associated Student Government, Hartford Branch, 1977-1978 (Box 2:, Folder 44)
  - Auditor, Federation of Students and Service Organizations, Storrs, 1976-1978 (Box 2:, Folder 45)
  - Auditor, University of Connecticut, 1976-1978 (Box 2:, Folder 46)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1970-1974 (Box 2:, Folder 47)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1974-1977 (Box 2:, Folder 48)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1974-1978 (Box 2:, Folder 49)
  - Australia, 1970 (Box 2:, Folder 50)
  - Autonomy, 1964-1972 (Box 2:, Folder 51)
  - Auxiliary Services, 1966-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 52)
  - Awards and donations, 1977-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 53)
  - Bachelor of General Studies Program, 1974-1978 (Box 2:, Folder 54)
  - Bakke Decision, 1978 (Box 2:, Folder 55)
  - Barney House, 1974-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 56)
  - Bartlett Arboretum, 1967-1971 (Box OS, 2:, Folder 57)
  - Beach (Louise C.) Memorial Collection, 1928-1968 (Box 2:, Folder 58-59)
  - Beach (Louise C.) Memorial Collection, 1967-1980 (Box 2:, Folder 60)
  - Beck, Audrey, 1972 (Box 2:, Folder 61)
  - Benton, William (Senator), 1964-1965 (Box 2:, Folder 62)
  - Bicycles, 1967-1968 (Box 2:, Folder 63)
  - Bikeway--Route 195, 1974-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 64)
  - Biobehavioral Sciences, 1970-1978 (Box 2:, Folder 65)
  - Biological Sciences Group, 1967-1977 (Box 2:, Folder 66)
  - Board Fee, 1975-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 67)
  - Board of Governor's (Student Union), 1970-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 68)
  - Board of Higher Education
    - Ad hoc Budget Committee, 1971 (Box 2:, Folder 69)
    - General Matters, 1977-1979 (Box 2:, Folder 70)
    - General Matters, 1979-1980 (Box 2:, Folder 71)
    - General Matters, 1977 (Box 3:, Folder 72)
    - Information System, 1976-1977 (Box 3:, Folder 73)
    - Reorganization of Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 74)
  - Bond Commission, 1969-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 75)
  - Bonds, 1971-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 76)
  - Bookstore, 1919 (Box 3:, Folder 77)
  - Bookstore (new), 1974-1975 (Box 3:, Folder 78)
  - Bookstore (new), 1975-1977 (Box 3:, Folder 79)
  - Bookstore (new), 1978 (Box 3:, Folder 80)
  - Bookstore (new), 1978-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 81)
  - Bookstore, Advisory Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 82)
  - Bookstore, Etherington Report, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder 83)
  - Bookstore, Task force on, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder 84)
  - Borge, Victor, 1964 (Box 3:, Folder 85)
  - Branch Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 3:, Folder 86)
  - Branch Fee Distribution, 1976-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 87)
  - Branch Fee Distribution, returned fees, 1977-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 88)
  - Branch parking, 1969-1973 (Box 3:, Folder 89)
  - Branches, 1976-1978 (Box 3:, Folder 90)
  - Branford House, 1978-1979 (Box 3:, Folder 91)
  - Branford House, 1975-1977 (Box 3:, Folder 92-93)
  - Breakage Fees, 1971 (Box 3:, Folder 94)
  - Buckley Amendment, 1975 (Box 3:, Folder 95)
  - Budget
    - 1923-1925 (Box 3:, Folder 96)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 3:, Folder 97)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 3:, Folder 98)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 3:, Folder 99-100)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 3:, Folder 101)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 3:, Folder 102-103)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 4:, Folder 104)
    - Allotments, 1968, 1971 (Box 4:, Folder 105)
    - Approved, 1979-1980 (Box 4:, Folder 106)
    - Auxilliary, 1974-1977 (Box 4:, Folder 107)
    - Auxilliary--proposed, 1974-1977 (Box 4:, Folder 108)
    - Branches, 1972-1977 (Box 4:, Folder 109)
    - Capital, 1969 (Box 6:, Folder 172)
    - Capital, 1970-1976 (Box 6:, Folder 173)
    - Capital, 1978-1979 (Box 6:, Folder 174)
    - Capital Request, 1976-1977 (Box 4:, Folder 110)
    - Capital Request, 1979-1980 (Box 4:, Folder 111)
    - Codes, 1977-1979 (Box 4:, Folder 112)
    - Cutting, 1975-1976 (Box 4:, Folder 113)
    - Divisions, 1974-1976 (Box 4:, Folder 114)
    - Extension Service, 1923 (Box 4:, Folder 115)
    - Governor's, 1975-1976 (Box 4:, Folder 116)
    - Governor's, 1976-1977 (Box 4:, Folder 117)
    - Governor's, 1977-1978 (Box 4:, Folder 118)
    - Governor's, 1978-1979 (Box 4:, Folder 119)
    - Governor's, 1979-1980 (Box 4:, Folder 120)
    - Health Center--Program, 1978-1979 (Box 4:, Folder 121)
    - Health Center--Proposal, 1977-1978 (Box 4:, Folder 122)
    - Materials, 1979 (Box 4:, Folder 123)
    - Materials, 1979-1980 (Box 4:, Folder 124-126)
    - Operating, 1969-1971 (Box 4:, Folder 127)
    - Operating, 1972-1973 (Box 5:, Folder 128)
    - Operating, 1975-1979 (Box 5:, Folder 129)
    - Operating, 1977-1978 (Box 5:, Folder 130)
    - Operating, 1977-1978 (Box 5:, Folder 131)
    - Operating, Request, 1969-1971 (Box 5:, Folder 132)
    - Operating, Request, 1971-1973 (Box 5:, Folder 133)
    - Operating, Request, 1973-1974 (Box 5:, Folder 134)
    - Operating, Request, 1977-1978 (Box 5:, Folder 135)
    - Operating, Request, 1977-1980 (Box 5:, Folder 136)
    - Operating, Request, 1978-1979 (Box 5:, Folder 137)
    - Presentation, 1978 (Box 5:, Folder 138)
    - Program, 1976-1977 (Box 5:, Folder 139)
    - Program, 1978-1979 (Box 5:, Folder 140)
    - Program, 1979-1980 (Box 5:, Folder 141-142)
    - Program, 1980-1981 (Box 5:, Folder 143)
    - Program, 1982-1983 (Box 5:, Folder 144)
    - Program, 1985-1986 (Box 5:, Folder 145)
    - Program Analysis, 1976-1977 (Box 5:, Folder 146)
    - Program Planning, 1971-1976 (Box 5:, Folder 147)
    - Program, Request, 1979-1980 (Box 5:, Folder 148)
    - Proposal, 1974-1977 (Box 5:, Folder 149)
    - Proposal, 1976-1977 (Box 5:, Folder 150)
    - Proposed Operations, 1975-1979 (Box 5:, Folder 151)
    - Recommended, 1975-1979 (Box 5:, Folder 152)
    - Request, 1977-1978 (Box 5:, Folder 153)
    - Request, 1979-1980 (Box 5:, Folder 154-155)
    - Savings, 1975 (Box 6:, Folder 156)
    - Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station, 1925-1927 (Box 6:, Folder 157)
    - Summary, 1973-1976 (Box 6:, Folder 158)
    - Summary, Preliminary, 1979-1980 (Box 6:, Folder 159)
  - Budget and Finance Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 6:, Folder 160)
  - Building Names, 1974 (Box 6:, Folder 161)
  - Building Plaques, 1971-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 162)
  - Burger King, 1975 (Box 6:, Folder 163)
  - Bursar, 1977-1978 (Box 6:, Folder 164)
  - Bus Service, 1970-1975 (Box 6:, Folder 165)
  - Cabinet Meetings, 1979 July - August (Box 6:, Folder 167)
  - Cabinet Meetings, 1979 October - December (Box 6:, Folder 168)
  - California, 1977-1979 (Box 6:, Folder 169)
  - Campus Planning and Development, Advisory Committee on, 1973 (Box 6:, Folder 170)
  - Campus Planning and Development Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 171)
  - Capital Building program, 1972-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 175)
  - Capital Projects, 1976-1984 (Box 6:, Folder 176-177)
  - Capital Projects, 1978-1979 (Box 6:, Folder 178)
  - Capital Projects, 1979-1980 (Box 6:, Folder 179)
  - Capital Request, 1969-1971 (Box 6:, Folder 180)
  - Capital Request, 1969-1975 (Box 6:, Folder 181)
  - Capital Request, 1971-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 182)
  - Capital Request, 1973-1974 (Box 6:, Folder 183)
  - Capital Request, Campus/Health Center, 1972-1973 (Box 6:, Folder 184)
  - Cash Management, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 185)
  - Catalogues, 1974-1977 (Box 7:, Folder 186)
  - Cedar Swamp (Carey Property), 1964-1967 (Box 7:, Folder 187)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1976-1977 (Box 7:, Folder 188)
  - Centennial Coordinating Committee (Box 7:, Folder 189)
  - Center for Black Studies, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 190)
  - Center for Environment and Man, 1971-1973 (Box 11:, Folder 343)
  - Center for Instructional Media and Technology, 1976-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 191)
  - Center for Italian Studies, Executive Committee, 1974 (Box 7:, Folder 192)
  - Center for the Study of Alcohol and Drug Problems, 1976-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 193)
  - Change and Innovation Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 7:, Folder 194)
  - Chemical Wate (disposal system), 1978-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 195)
  - Churches, 1965-1969 (Box 7:, Folder 196)
  - Central Naugatuck Valley (Higher Education Center), 1967-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 197)
  - Civil Defense, 1969-1978 (Box 7:, Folder 198)
  - Civil Defense Advisory Committee, 1973 (Box 7:, Folder 199)
  - Civil Liberties Union, 1974 (Box 7:, Folder 200)
  - Claims Commission, 1975 (Box 7:, Folder 201)
  - Clerical Pool, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 202)
  - Clerical Training Program, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 203)
  - Coast Guard, 1971-1974 (Box 7:, Folder 204)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1977-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 205-206)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1978-1980 (Box 7:, Folder 207)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 208)
  - Collective Bargaining, Classified, 1977 (Box 7:, Folder 209)
  - College of Liberal Arts and Sciences, 1963-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 210)
  - College of Liberal Arts and Sciences, 1975-1977 (Box 7:, Folder 211)
  - College Theatre, 1962-1968 (Box 7:, Folder 212)
  - Commercial Block Appraisal, 1968 (Box 7:, Folder 213)
  - Commercial Properties Rental Facilities Management
    - 1949-1970 (Box OS, 7:, Folder 214)
    - 1971-1976 (Box 7:, Folder 215)
    - 1977 (Box 7:, Folder 216)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 7:, Folder 217)
    - 1979 (Box 7:, Folder 218)
  - Commission for Higher Education
    - 1970 (Box 7:, Folder 219)
    - 1971 (Box 7:, Folder 220)
    - 1977 (Box 7:, Folder 221)
    - Annual report, 1972 (Box 7:, Folder 222)
    - Auxillary Services, 1971 (Box 7:, Folder 223)
    - Budget, 1968-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 224)
    - Budget Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 8:, Folder 225)
    - Budget Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 8:, Folder 226)
    - Community Colleges, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 227)
    - Fees, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 228)
    - Goals, 1969 (Box 8:, Folder 229)
    - Guidelines, 1968 (Box 8:, Folder 230)
    - Health Center, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 231)
    - Higher Education legislation, 1972 (Box 8:, Folder 232)
    - Information for Appropriations Committee, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 233)
    - Legal, 1973 (Box 8:, Folder 234)
    - Master Plan, 1972-1973 (Box 8:, Folder 235)
    - Organization, ca. 1967-1968 (Box 8:, Folder 236)
    - Personnel, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 237)
    - Philosophy, 1970 (Box 8:, Folder 238)
    - Planning, 1970 (Box 8:, Folder 239)
    - Planning Funds, 1970 (Box 8:, Folder 240)
    - Projects, 1972 (Box 8:, Folder 241)
    - Request, 1972-1973 (Box 8:, Folder 242)
    - Statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 8:, Folder 243)
    - Surveys and statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 8:, Folder 244)
    - Task Force III (Financing), 1970-1971 (Box 8:, Folder 245)
    - Tuition, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 246)
    - University History, 1971 (Box 8:, Folder 247)
  - Commission on Aid to Higher Education, 1963, 1969 (Box 8:, Folder 248)
  - Committees--Dismiss (tentative), 1974 (Box 8:, Folder 249)
  - Committees--Standing (University), 1969-1973 (Box 8:, Folder 250)
  - Committee of Three, 1973-1974 (Box 8:, Folder 251)
  - Committee of Three, 1979 (Box 8:, Folder 252)
  - Commons Dining Hall, 1977-1979 (Box 8:, Folder 253)
  - Commons Dining Hall Renovation, 1976-1977 (Box 8:, Folder 254)
  - Community Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 8:, Folder 255)
  - Community Affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 8:, Folder 256)
  - Community Colleges, 1966-1978 (Box 8:, Folder 257)
  - Community Development Action Plan (CDAP)
    - Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 8:, Folder 258)
    - Town of Mansfield, 1968-1969 (Box 8:, Folder 259)
    - Subcommittee on Economic Development, 1969-1970 (Box 8:, Folder 260)
  - Commuter's Union, 1974-1976 (Box 8:, Folder 261)
  - Complaints, 1975-1977 (Box 8:, Folder 262)
  - Complaints, 1978-1979 (Box 8:, Folder 263)
  - Computer--MSA, 1977 (Box 8:, Folder 264)
  - Computing, Student Data Systems, 1979-1981 (Box 8:, Folder 265)
  - Computer Center
    - 1978-1980 (Box 9:, Folder 266-268)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 9:, Folder 272-275)
    - 1979 (Box 9:, Folder 269-271)
    - Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 9:, Folder 276)
  - Condominium Housing, 1975 (Box 9:, Folder 277)
  - Connecticut Business and Industry Association, 1974 (Box 9:, Folder 278)
  - Connecticut Daily Campus, 1975-1978 (Box 9:, Folder 279)
  - Connecticut Historical Commission, 1978 (Box 9:, Folder 280)
  - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1975 (Box 9:, Folder 281)
  - CONNPEP, 1974-1977 (Box 9:, Folder 282)
  - CONNPIRG, 1974-1977 (Box 9:, Folder 283)
  - Connecticut Society of Executives, undated, 1925-1926 (Box 9:, Folder 284)
  - Connecticut State Employees Association (CSEA), 1970-1974 (Box 9:, Folder 285)
  - Connecticut State Employees Information System, 1977 (Box 9:, Folder 286)
  - Connecticut State Employees Information System, 1978 (Box 9:, Folder 287)
  - Connecticut Natural Gas Company, 1967-1968 (Box 9:, Folder 288)
  - Conntac, 1970 (Box 9:, Folder 289)
  - Construction Projects--Status, 1971-1974 (Box 9:, Folder 290)
  - Consulting Services, 1970-1977 (Box 9:, Folder 291)
  - Continuing and Extended Education Dean--Search, 1975 (Box 9:, Folder 292)
  - Continuing Education Services, 1967-1979 (Box 9:, Folder 293)
  - Contracts, 1971-1976 (Box 9:, Folder 294)
  - Contract and Grant Information System, 1975-1978 (Box 9:, Folder 295)
  - Controller, 1963-1979 (Box 9:, Folder 296)
  - Cooperative Education, 1966-1973 (Box 9:, Folder 297)
  - Coordinating Council for the Board of Trustees
    - 1976 (Box 10:, Folder 298-299)
    - 1977 (Box 10:, Folder 300)
    - 1978 (Box 10:, Folder 301)
  - Copyright Policy Committee, 1972-1978 (Box 10:, Folder 302)
  - Council of Presidents, 1978 (Box 10:, Folder 303)
  - Credit Unions, 1971-1979 (Box 10:, Folder 304)
  - Data Processing Department, 1970-1977 (Box 10:, Folder 305)
  - Data Processing Department, 1974-1977 (Box 10:, Folder 306)
  - Dawson Development Plan, undated (Box 10:, Folder 307)
  - Day Care Center, 1970-1971 (Box 10:, Folder 308)
  - Debt Retirement, 1963-1971 (Box 10:, Folder 309)
  - Deferred Compensation Plan, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 310)
  - Deferred Maintenance, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 311)
  - Development, 1977 (Box 10:, Folder 312)
  - Development Administrators Training Program, 1970-1976 (Box 10:, Folder 313)
  - Development Coordinating Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 10:, Folder 314)
  - Development Office, 1970-1978 (Box 10:, Folder 315)
  - Dining Halls, 1972-1976 (Box 10:, Folder 316)
  - Discretionary Funds, 1967, 1970 (Box 10:, Folder 317)
  - Division of Residence Halls and Food Service, 1966-1972 (Box 10:, Folder 318)
  - Dog Lane Project (Town - University), 1975-1977 (Box OS, 10:, Folder 319)
  - Dogs, 1971-1978 (Box 10:, Folder 320)
  - Dormitory Fire Codes, 1978-1979 (Box 10:, Folder 321-322)
  - Drugs, 1971 (Box 10:, Folder 323)
  - Education Administration, 1979 (Box 10:, Folder 324)
  - Education Committee (Legislative), 1967-1969 (Box 10:, Folder 325)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories, 1972-1975 (Box 10:, Folder 326)
  - Emergency Power for Residence Halls, 1972-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 327)
  - Emergency Preparedness, 1975 (Box 10:, Folder 328)
  - Employee - Stenographers Time, 1922-1923 (Box 10:, Folder 329)
  - Employee's Assistance Program, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 330)
  - Employee's Assistance Program Committee, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 331)